A Guide to the William J. “Bill” Elvin Collection, 1914-2004, bulk 1963-2003
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 3: Photographs, 1956-2003
  - Nike Missile Site - Springvale Road, 1993 August (Box 29)
  - Niklaus, David C., 1989 (Box 29)
  - Nixon protestors, Undated (Box 29)
  - Nolan, Robert A., Undated (Box 29)
  - Nordstrom's - Opening with June Williams, Earle Williams, Bill Elvin, Catherine Filene Shouse, 1988 March 3 (Box 29)
  - Norris, William R., 1985 (Box 29)
  - North, Oliver, 1993 (Box 29)
  - Northern Telecom, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Northern Virginia Savings and Loan, Undated (Box 29)
  - Norton, William R., Undated (Box 29)
  - Nothhaft, Henry R., Undated (Box 29)
  - Nussbaum, Jay H., 1984 (Box 29)
  - Nyman, Thomas H., Undated (Box 29)
  - O'Brien, Mary Frances, Undated (Box 29)
  - O'Connell, James P., Undated (Box 29)
  - Odeen, Karla, Undated (Box 29)
  - Odom, Bill, Undated (Box 29)
  - O'Donnell, Justin C., Undated (Box 29)
  - O'Flaherty, Daniel Fairfax, Undated (Box 29)
  - Ogden, Alan, Undated (Box 29)
  - Ogle, David E., 1978 (Box 29)
  - Oil Spill, Undated (Box 29)
  - Olander, Dick, Undated (Box 29)
  - Old Dominion Drive and Chain Bridge Road, Undated (Box 29)
  - Old Dominion Drive and Dolley Madison Boulevard, Undated (Box 29)
  - Old Firehouse Teen Center, Undated (Box 29)
  - Olin, Charles H., Undated (Box 29)
  - O'Meara, Peter, Undated (Box 29)
  - O'Neil, Kevin, 1989 (Box 29)
  - Opper, David, Undated (Box 29)
  - Opstad, Donald O., Undated (Box 29)
  - Ore, William E., 1989 (Box 29)
  - Orland Street Trail, 1990 May 30 (Box 29)
  - Ortmann, Michael R., Undated (Box 29)
  - Orton, Joan, Undated (Box 29)
  - Ouellette, Robert P., 1983 (Box 29)
  - Ould, James, Undated (Box 29)
  - Owen, Ferris S., 1985 (Box 29)
  - Owen, Kenneth, Undated (Box 29)
  - Oxaal, Leif, Undated (Box 29)
  - Oyster, Elizabeth, Undated (Box 29)
  - Packaging Store, Undated (Box 29)
  - Packard, Jean, 1969 (Box 29)
  - Padrick, Jack O., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pahlavi, Reza, Undated (Box 29)
  - Paige, Hilliard W., 1985 (Box 29)
  - Paine, Patricia Young, 1978 (Box 29)
  - Pal, Dr. Gopal S., 1985 (Box 29)
  - Pala, William P., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pande, Vijay Satyanand, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pangman, Hale G., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pant, Shiva K., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pappas, Pete, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Parker, Col. David B., 1957 (Box 29)
  - Parker, Herbert, 1975 (Box 29)
  - Parker, Joan, 1989 (Box 29)
  - Parker, Lutrelle F., Sr., Undated (Box 29)
  - Parker, Mette R., 1984 (Box 29)
  - Parris, Stan, 1989 (Box 29)
  - Parvezian, Allen - with Antoinette C. MacAulay, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pask, James B., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pastor, Marianne V., 1986 (Box 29)
  - Patowmack Canal, 1993 March 6 (Box 29)
  - Pattison, Daniel J., Undated (Box 29)
  - Payne, Dr. Marlene, 1982 (Box 29)
  - Payne, Vernon, Undated (Box 29)
  - Paynter, Dr. Orville E., Undated (Box 29)
  - Peacock House, Undated (Box 29)
  - Peed, Carl R., 1990-1991 (Box 29)
  - Pennington, Pamela J., 1984 (Box 29)
  - Perine, Wilbur B., Jr., Undated (Box 29)
  - Perlich, Richard H., Undated (Box 29)
  - Perlik, William R., Undated (Box 29)
  - Perot, Ross, Undated (Box 29)
  - Perper, Martin, Undated (Box 29)
  - Perry, Charles B., II, 1986 (Box 29)
  - Perry, Stanley D., Undated (Box 29)
  - Peters, Richard, Undated (Box 29)
  - Petty, Rev. James S., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pfotenhauer, Robert P., 1987 (Box 29)
  - Phares, Susan, Undated (Box 29)
  - Phillips, Barbara, Undated (Box 29)
  - Phillips, G. Conoly, Undated (Box 29)
  - Phillips, James H., 1986 (Box 29)
  - Phillips, Rufus, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pickell, Charles N., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pierce, Almot, 1992 (Box 29)
  - Pierce, Merrily, 2003 (Box 29)
  - Pierson, Carol, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pierson, Michael C., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pinder, Rev. Gary, Undated (Box 29)
  - Piscopo, Lezah, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pittaro, Adm. George F., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pla, Kika Silva, Undated (Box 29)
  - Platcow, Richard, 1985 (Box 29)
  - Pleasant Grove Church, 1980-1993 (Box 29)
  - Ploskina, Bill, Undated (Box 29)
  - Plouffe, Robert, Undated (Box 29)
  - Plum, Kenneth R., 1987 (Box 29)
  - Poehler, P. Henry, Undated (Box 29)
  - Poehner, Mildred, Undated (Box 29)
  - Poling, Harold "Reds", 1991 July 4 (Box 29)
  - Poling, Ted and Martha, 1989 (Box 29)
  - Polk, Sidney, 1984 (Box 29)
  - Polk, Warren and Joan, Undated (Box 29)
  - Polley, R. Stephen, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pomeroy, Michael, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pond, Jesse, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pond, Peggy, Undated (Box 29)
  - Ponder, Sherman, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Poole, Richard, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Pope, Donna, Undated (Box 29)
  - Poretz, Dr. Donald M., 1985 (Box 29)
  - Poretz, Douglas, 1987 (Box 29)
  - Porter, Clifford L., 1963 (Box 29)
  - Potomac River, 1972 (Box 29)
  - Potomac School, 1989 (Box 29)
  - Potter, Charles E., Undated (Box 29)
  - Potthast, Joey, Undated (Box 29)
  - Potts, Robert A., Undated (Box 29)
  - Poucher, Wayne, Undated (Box 29)
  - Poulton, Edgar E., Undated (Box 29)
  - Poulton, Peg, Undated (Box 29)
  - Powers, David R., 1979 (Box 29)
  - Powers, Loyd T., Jr., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pratt, Douglas M., Undated (Box 29)
  - Price, Julie Erin, Undated (Box 29)
  - Price, Keith, Undated (Box 29)
  - Prichard Home, Undated (Box 29)
  - Pritz, Michael D., Undated (Box 29)
  - Proctor, Douglas E., 1973 (Box 29)
  - Prominski, Dr. John E., Undated (Box 29)
  - Providence Baptist Church, 1990 (Box 29)
  - Pryor, Stephen D., Undated (Box 29)
  - Pugh, Joel, Undated (Box 29)
  - Purvis, Richard C., Undated (Box 29)
  - Putbrese, Kelan Keith, Undated (Box 29)
  - Quale, Dan, Undated (Box 29)
  - Quayle, Marilyn, Undated (Box 29)
  - QuestTech, Undated (Box 29)
  - Quilty, John S., 1986 (Box 29)
  - Quinn, Michael A., Undated (Box 29)
  - Quirion, C. Arnie, Undated (Box 29)
  - Ragan, Linda H., Undated (Box 29)
  - Ragone, David V., Undated (Box 29)
  - Rahall, Rebecca, Undated (Box 30)
  - Ralls, Jane, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Ramada Hotel - Tysons Corner, Undated (Box 30)
  - Ramsay, William W., Undated (Box 30)
  - Ramsey, Maj. Gen. Lloyd B., 1970 (Box 30)
  - Randle, Mary, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Ranleigh Manor, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rapport, Richard J. and Christy, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rapport, Richard J. (with George E. Kranda, Carroll D. Buracker, and John J. Whalen), 1984 (Box 30)
  - Rasmussen, Kathy Z., 1984-1987 (Box 30)
  - Ratcliff, Ted, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rathgeber, Linda, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rauner, Harold C., 1987 (Box 30)
  - Raven, Paul R., 1986 (Box 30)
  - Rawlings, George C., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Reckmeyer, Anthony D., 1983 (Box 30)
  - Recycling, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Reed, Margaret H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Reed, T. Dean, 1981 (Box 30)
  - Regan, Donald T., 1985 (Box 30)
  - Reger, Joe, Undated (Box 30)
  - Register, Ethel Wilcox, Undated (Box 30)
  - Reiben, Paul, Undated (Box 30)
  - Reichardt, David L., 1986 (Box 30)
  - Reichbauer, Louis C., Undated (Box 30)
  - Reid, James R., Undated (Box 30)
  - Reid, Richard, Undated (Box 30)
  - Reid, Robert H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Reilly, Philip M., Undated (Box 30)
  - Reilly, William K., Undated (Box 30)
  - Reston Animal Farm, 1993 April (Box 30)
  - Reynolds, Paul, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rhea, George C., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rhoads, Bruce C. "Dusty", Undated (Box 30)
  - Rice, Betsy, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rice, James M., 1983 (Box 30)
  - Rice, John S., 1974 (Box 30)
  - Richards, Lilla, 1987-1992 (Box 30)
  - Richards, Stan, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Richardson, David W., 1984 (Box 30)
  - Ridder, Marie, Undated (Box 30)
  - Ridgely, E. Guy, Undated (Box 30)
  - Ridgely, Robert, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rieger, Charles J., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rieger, Linda, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rietzke, Eugene H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rife, Marty L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Riggs Bank, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Riley, Ivan H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Riordan, Patricia M., 1982 (Box 30)
  - Riverbend Park, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rizik, Peter, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rob (unidentified bass player), 1994 October 9 (Box 30)
  - Robb, Charles "Chuck", 1987-1991 (Box 30)
  - Robb, Lynda, Undated (Box 30)
  - Roberts, Alan J., 1984 (Box 30)
  - Roberts, Bob, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Roberts, Carren B., Undated (Box 30)
  - Roberts, Kitty L., 1990 (Box 30)
  - Roberts, Lawrence G., Undated (Box 30)
  - Roberts, Sam A., Undated (Box 30)
  - Roberts, William G., 1990 (Box 30)
  - Robertson, Hugh L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Robertson, Dr. James L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Robeson, Stuart H., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Robinette, Bruce, 1984 (Box 30)
  - Robinson, Clarence A., Sr., 1990 (Box 30)
  - Robinson, James W., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rocco's Italian Restaurant, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rockefeller, Jay, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rockwell, George Lincoln, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rodriguez, Undated (Box 30)
  - Roe, Juanita, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rohrbaugh, Dorsey, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rokeby, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Rolfs, Henry J., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rollison, Jack, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rolufs, Larry E., 1982 (Box 30)
  - Romberg, Caroline M., Undated (Box 30)
  - Roop, William B., 1974 (Box 30)
  - Roosevelt, Dan, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rosenbaum, Albert B., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rosenbaum, Mary Anne, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rosenbaum, Robert, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rosenbaum, Sara E., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rosenberger, Francis Coleman, 1971 (Box 30)
  - Rosenblum, Howard E., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rotary Club, Undated (Box 30)
  - Roth, Jeff, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Roth, Liz, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rothenberg, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rothrock, Elizabeth, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Rothrock, Thomas J., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rotonda Condominium, 1978-1993 (Box 30)
  - Rouse, Daniel J., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rouse, David, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Rowland, Mrs. James, Undated (Box 30)
  - Ruck, F. Lee, 1973 (Box 30)
  - Rucker, William B., 1986 (Box 30)
  - Rudolph, Dolores M., Undated (Box 30)
  - Ruffino, John, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rugh, Mrs. Timothy, Undated (Box 30)
  - Ruppel, Warren, Undated (Box 30)
  - Ruppert, M. Frank, Undated (Box 30)
  - Rush, Orville F., Undated (Box 30)
  - Russell, Dr. James E., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rust, John H., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rust, Robert, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Rust, Thomas D., Undated (Box 30)
  - Ruthling, Ann C., Undated (Box 30)
  - Ruthrock, Judge John A., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rutledge, Talmadge G., Undated (Box 30)
  - Ryan, Bob, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Ryan, Dr. Robert F., Undated (Box 30)
  - Rzewinicki, John J., 1980 (Box 30)
  - Sachs, George A., 1991 (Box 30)
  - Sacirbey, Nedzib, Undated (Box 30)
  - Safeway (Chain Bridge Road), Undated (Box 30)
  - SAIC Building, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Sakach, Sister Mary Elizabeth, Undated (Box 30)
  - Salem, Robert J., Undated (Box 30)
  - Saliba, Issam, Undated (Box 30)
  - Salona Encampment, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sam's Deli, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Sam's Sunoco, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sanders, David G., 1991 (Box 30)
  - Sanderson, T.C. (Tim), Undated (Box 30)
  - Sanford, Leonard E., 1984 (Box 30)
  - Santoro, Michael R., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sargent, Alice, 1992 (Box 30)
  - Sassparilla with Laurel Blaydes, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sawyer, Mary Ellen - with Marshall Seymour, Undated (Box 30)
  - Scalise, Richard C., Undated (Box 30)
  - Scarborough, Edward, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schar, Dwight C., 1987-1989 (Box 30)
  - Schar, Jan, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schell, John, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schellhorn, Joseph R., Undated (Box 30)
  - Schelling, John P., Undated (Box 30)
  - Schick, Kenneth D., 1983 (Box 30)
  - Schivaia, Milvia, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schlesinger, James R., 1987 (Box 30)
  - Schlipf, Carolyn, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schmidt, Fred J., Undated (Box 30)
  - School Bonds - with Charles Robb, Lynda Robb, Mary Anne Lecos, Ed Anderson, and William S. Hoofnagle, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schools, Charles H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Schreer, Andrew, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schreiner, Dr. George E., Undated (Box 30)
  - Schultz, Leslie P., 1984 (Box 30)
  - Schultz, Nancy, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schulze, Richard T., Undated (Box 30)
  - Schumacher, Paul, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schutzengel, Dr. Daniella, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Schwartz, Ann, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schwartz, Dr. H. Randall, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schwartz, Dr. Richard, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Schweiker, Claire, Undated (Box 30)
  - Schweiker, Richard, Undated (Box 30)
  - Scott, Gail, Undated (Box 30)
  - Scott, James M., 1991 (Box 30)
  - Scott, Marilyn, Undated (Box 30)
  - Scott, William L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Scotts Run Falls, Undated (Box 30)
  - Scoville Property, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Scullt, Mark, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Searle, Robert W., Undated (Box 30)
  - Searles, P. David, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sebrell, T.E., III, Undated (Box 30)
  - Secretary's Friend, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sedam, Glenn J., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Seely, Rebecca, Undated (Box 30)
  - Selden, Richard T., Undated (Box 30)
  - Semales, Bob, Undated (Box 30)
  - Seneca Road - Construction, 1993 (Box 30)
  - 7-Eleven, 1990 (Box 30)
  - Seward, R. Brinkley, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shacochis, Bob, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shacochis, John P., Undated (Box 30)
  - Shafer, Ronald G., 1988 (Box 30)
  - Shafran, George P., 1986 (Box 30)
  - Shapiro, Leonard A., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sharon Masonic Lodge - 999 Balls Hill Road, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Sharrett, Allan C., Undated (Box 30)
  - Shaw, Albert, III, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shaw, Mrs. Albert III, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shaw, Harold "Ranger Hal", 1977-1986 (Box 30)
  - Sheets, Rev. Forrest, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shelp, Page, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shelton, Wayne, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sher, Margery Leveen, 1986 (Box 30)
  - Sheraton Premiere Hotel, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sheridan, Kenneth T., 1986 (Box 30)
  - Sherk, Rev. Grant R., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sherwood, John M., Undated (Box 30)
  - Shin, Sam - McLean Sunoco, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Shipley, R.L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Short, Laurence A., Undated (Box 30)
  - Shotwell, Mike, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shoup, Ann, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Shoup, Charles, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shouse, Catherine, Undated (Box 30)
  - Shouse, Catherine Filene, 1978 (Box 30)
  - Shrader, Ralph W., Undated (Box 30)
  - Shumaker, James L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sielert, John R., 1989 (Box 30)
  - Siess, Mrs. Mayhew, 1983 (Box 30)
  - Simmons, Arlis, Undated (Box 30)
  - Simmons, Howell B., Undated (Box 30)
  - Simmons, Kathy, Undated (Box 30)
  - Simmons, Kendall W., Undated (Box 30)
  - Simon, David, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Simons, Jane, Undated (Box 30)
  - Simpson, Kathryn L., 1985 (Box 30)
  - Sinback, Warner R., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sinks, Thomas W., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sipe, Harry, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sirvio, Anna, 1991 (Box 30)
  - Skubal, Alan, 1991 (Box 30)
  - Skunda, Robert T., Undated (Box 30)
  - Slaybaugh, John C., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sloan, Alys, Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Byron Albert, Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Claude H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Dr. David, Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, David L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Gail, 1981 (Box 30)
  - Smith, Janet, Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Rev. John Preston, Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Larry, 1987 (Box 30)
  - Smith, Ralph C., Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Robert D., Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Stephen L., 1982 (Box 30)
  - Smith, Verlin W., Undated (Box 30)
  - Smith, Zena, Undated (Box 30)
  - Snavely, William P., Undated (Box 30)
  - Snider, Edwin W., 1980 (Box 30)
  - Snider, Hubert D., Undated (Box 30)
  - Snowdon, Richard W., 1986 (Box 30)
  - Snyder, Anise, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sodergren, Katherine, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sokolove, K. Stanley, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sollenberger, Howard E., 1976 (Box 30)
  - Sommovigo, Susan, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Sonnenday, Rev. John W., 1982 (Box 30)
  - Sophisticat Botique, Undated (Box 30)
  - Soresi, Carl D., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sours, Joyce F., 1984 (Box 30)
  - Sousa, Walter R., 1985 (Box 30)
  - South, Lynda J., 1984 (Box 30)
  - Spagnoli, John J., Undated (Box 30)
  - Spangenberg, George A., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sparger, John, Undated (Box 30)
  - Spencer, Robert T., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sperling, Philip I., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sperry Univac Building, Undated (Box 30)
  - Spinetta, Frank, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sprenkel, Dr. Dale H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Spring Hill Business Center, 1989 (Box 30)
  - Spring Hill Elementary School, Undated (Box 30)
  - Spring Hill Recreation Center, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Spring Hill Road and Lewinsville Road Intersection, 1993 (Box 30)
  - Springer, John C., 1978 (Box 30)
  - St. John's Catholic Church, Undated (Box 30)
  - St. John's Episcopal Church Rectory, Undated (Box 30)
  - St. Luke's Catholic Church, 1983 (Box 30)
  - St. Mary's Catholich Church - Bayard Evans, Fr. Joseph W. Hursch, and Joyce Wilkinson presenting plaque, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Stabile, Mary Ann, Undated (Box 30)
  - Stables, Rev. A.G., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stalcup, Dana, Undated (Box 30)
  - Stalcup's Christmas Trees, Undated (Box 30)
  - Staley, Mrs. David L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stamm, Gilbert, Undated (Box 30)
  - Stapleton, John, Undated (Box 30)
  - Starnes, Richard, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Starr, Alice M., Undated (Box 30)
  - Starr, Kenneth W., 1990 (Box 30)
  - Starr, Stuart H., 1986 (Box 30)
  - Stearns, Darrel H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stebbins, Col. Russell, Undated (Box 30)
  - Steele, Sidney R., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stegemeier, R.J., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stein, Prof. Julian, 1982 (Box 30)
  - Steiner, Walter D., 1986 (Box 30)
  - Stein-Schneider, Dr. Herbert, Undated (Box 30)
  - Stephens, Sinah K. L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stephens, Walter L., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stetten, Kenneth J., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stevens, Dr. George E. - with son Frank Stevens, 1993 June 30 (Box 30)
  - Stevens, Thomas M., 1988 (Box 30)
  - Stevens, William B., 1984 (Box 30)
  - Stewart, Ruth, Undated (Box 30)
  - Stewart, William, Undated (Box 30)
  - Stitt, David T., 1991 (Box 30)
  - Stockmeyer, Steven F., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stoiko, Margaret Jane, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Stone, James C., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stone, Roy A., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stotsky, James S., Undated (Box 30)
  - Strauss, Jane, 1991 (Box 30)
  - Structural Clay Products Institute Building, 1968 (Box 30)
  - Stryker, Russell F., Jr., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stuart, Casey, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Stubblebine, Albert N., Undated (Box 30)
  - Stull, C. Meade, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sturtevant, Rev. William L., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sugarman, Jule, Undated (Box 30)
  - Sullivan, Mike, Undated (Box 30)
  - Summers, Beulah, 1983 (Box 30)
  - Summers, Gale, Undated (Box 30)
  - Summers, John K., 1984 (Box 30)
  - Sun, Eric, 1988 (Box 30)
  - Sundquist, Beth R., Undated (Box 30)
  - Surovell, Robert J., Undated (Box 30)
  - Sutcliffe, Joyce, 1983 (Box 30)
  - Sutherland, David A., Undated (Box 30)
  - Swadley, Virgil H., Undated (Box 30)
  - Swanson, Sally, Undated (Box 30)
  - Swanzy, Gene, 1982 (Box 30)
  - Swinson, James D. "Jim", 1986 (Box 30)
  - Syverson, Hope, 1976 (Box 30)
  - Tabler, Charles B., 1979 (Box 31)
  - Tabor, Robert R., Undated (Box 31)
  - Taliaferro, Henry, Undated (Box 31)
  - Taliaferro, Mrs., Undated (Box 31)
  - Taliaferro, Sarah Stewart, Undated (Box 31)
  - Talley, Robert P., Undated (Box 31)
  - Tamillow, Michael, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tappan, Thomas W., Undated (Box 31)
  - Tart, Dr. Nelson M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Tartaro, Sybil, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tate, James R., 1972 (Box 31)
  - Tatum, Rev. William J., Undated (Box 31)
  - Teel, S. Martin, Jr., 1988 (Box 31)
  - Temple Rodef Shalom, Undated (Box 31)
  - Temple, Bliss, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tenney, Marlis, Undated (Box 31)
  - Terry, Mary Sue, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Terry, Parshelle, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Thatcher, John, 1991 (Box 31)
  - Thatcher, Margaret, 1995 (Box 31)
  - This, Jeanine, Undated (Box 31)
  - This, Leslie E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Thoburn, Lloyd, 1987 (Box 31)
  - Thoburn, Robert L., 1987 (Box 31)
  - Thomas, Lydia, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Thompson, Albert P., Undated (Box 31)
  - Thompson, Joan, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Thompson, Pauline, Undated (Box 31)
  - Thompson, Stanley E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Thorpe, Lee, Undated (Box 31)
  - Thorpe, Tony W., 1988 (Box 31)
  - Threadgill, Eugene, Undated (Box 31)
  - Thurmond, Nancy, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Thurmond, Strom, Undated (Box 31)
  - Thurner, Patricia, Undated (Box 31)
  - Thursz, Dr. Daniel, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Tichenor, Gerald E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Tighe, Kevin, Undated (Box 31)
  - Till, Chris, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Tillotson, Robert G., Undated (Box 31)
  - Timms, Albert G., Undated (Box 31)
  - Tingey, Earl C., Undated (Box 31)
  - Tipton, John "Jet", Undated (Box 31)
  - Tisinger, Mary, Undated (Box 31)
  - Todd, Christopher Adam, Undated (Box 31)
  - Todd, James W., Undated (Box 31)
  - Toivonen, Arnold A., 1987 (Box 31)
  - Tombes, Averett S., 1981 (Box 31)
  - Tot Olympics, Undated (Box 31)
  - Toulme, Nill V., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Toups, John M., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Towner, Alonzo A., Undated (Box 31)
  - Townsend, Florence E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Trash Parkouts, Undated (Box 31)
  - Travelstead, Timothy C., 1987 (Box 31)
  - Traylor, Lawrence, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tressler, Ernest, 1975 (Box 31)
  - Trinity United Methodist Church, Undated (Box 31)
  - Trisler, William F., Jr., Undated (Box 31)
  - Trobaugh, Diane, Undated (Box 31)
  - Trueax, Alfred W., Undated (Box 31)
  - Trueax, Mary, 1991 (Box 31)
  - Trumble, Eric R., Undated (Box 31)
  - Tsitos, Pamela, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Tuck, Leslie, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Tull, Ronald I., Undated (Box 31)
  - Turnage, Martha A., Undated (Box 31)
  - Tuttle, Dawn, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tycon Courthouse - Dedication with Charles Robb, James Lewis, Martha Pennino, and Jack Herrity, 1983 (Box 31)
  - Tyl, Noel, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tysons II Sign, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tysons Corner Center, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Tysons Corner Center - Woodward & Lothrop and Hot Shoppes Cafeteria, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tysons Double-Decker Buses, Undated (Box 31)
  - Tysons Enterprise Center, 1979 (Box 31)
  - Tysons Ice Rink, 1976 (Box 31)
  - Tysons skyline, 1993 (Box 31)
  - Udall, Morris - House on Long Meadow Road, 1988 (Box 31)
  - Uhlaner, Dr. Julius E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Underground Wiring, 1989 (Box 31)
  - Upson, Don, Undated (Box 31)
  - Urquhart, Glen T., Undated (Box 31)
  - Uzun, Zeynel, Undated (Box 31)
  - Valentine, Drew, Undated (Box 31)
  - Van Devanter, Jean M., Undated (Box 31)
  - Van Hollen, Christopher, 1972 (Box 31)
  - Van Meter, LaRue, Undated (Box 31)
  - Van Ness, Boyd, Undated (Box 31)
  - Van Over, Ginger, Undated (Box 31)
  - Van Wagoner, Lynette, 1977 (Box 31)
  - Van Winkle, Elisabeth, 1987 (Box 31)
  - Vanderwende, Mr. and Mrs. George, Undated (Box 31)
  - Vane, Linda, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Veirs, Alvin B., Jr., Undated (Box 31)
  - Venneberg, Ruth, 1981 (Box 31)
  - Venuto, Charles A., 1986 (Box 31)
  - Verhalen, Phyllis, Undated (Box 31)
  - Vick, Franklin, Undated (Box 31)
  - Vickery, Raymond, Undated (Box 31)
  - Vickery, Raymond E., Sr., 1987 (Box 31)
  - Victory, James E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Victory, Mary, Undated (Box 31)
  - Vignali, Mary, Undated (Box 31)
  - Vinson Hall, Undated (Box 31)
  - Virginia Power - Tysons Substation, Undated (Box 31)
  - Vogel, Nina, Undated (Box 31)
  - Vogeler, William K., Undated (Box 31)
  - Voight, Marianne, Undated (Box 31)
  - Volk, John L., Undated (Box 31)
  - Vollenwieder, David O., Undated (Box 31)
  - Voorhees, Ted, 1981 (Box 31)
  - Voskuil, Barbara, Undated (Box 31)
  - Waale, Ted, Undated (Box 31)
  - Waddell, Alexander, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Waddell, Charles, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wade, Evelyn, Undated (Box 31)
  - Wagstaff, Robert E., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wahl, John A., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wahlquist, Andrew, 1990 (Box 31)
  - Waldrop, Thomas E., 1984 (Box 31)
  - Walker, Bruce V., 1985 (Box 31)
  - Walker, Dorothy J., Undated (Box 31)
  - Walker, Mary, Undated (Box 31)
  - Walker, Pamela, 1984 (Box 31)
  - Walker, Preston L., Undated (Box 31)
  - Wall, Donna, Undated (Box 31)